(Howard:)Yes.
(Penny:)Those are also the side effects
(Penny:)of having a 75-year-old man
with an erection
(Penny:)climb on top of you.
(Bernadette:)Want to stop here?
(Penny:)Uh, no.
I can keep going.
(Bernadette:)Nah, you got this.
(Bernadette:)Let's go for a drink.
I'll call Amy.
(Penny:)Okay, good. She seemed like she
really wanted to go out tonight.
(ringtone playing)
(Amy(on phone):)Hey, girl.
(Leonard:)Okay, next question,
for the Butterfinger:
how long is a galactic year?
250 million years!
Yes!
(all cheering)
(Howard:)Okay, this one is
for a Cadbury Creme Egg.
(gasps)
It's not even Easter time.
This is crazy!
(Howard:)Which Archimedean solid
has 20 regular triangular faces,
(Howard:)30 square faces,
12 pentagonal faces,
(Howard:)60 vertices and 120 edges?
ALL:
The Rhombicosidodecahedron!
Yes!
(all cheering)
We are so smart!
(Raj:)Why didn't girls like us
in high school?
(Howard:)Because we were awkward and
weird and couldn't play sports!
Right again!